https://lijsoccer.com/privacy/

Privacy Statement
At Long Island Junior Soccer League (www.lijsoccer.com), our goal is to provide a fun, informative and safe interactive online experience for all of the children and parents who make up the LIJSL family. We want you to understand and feel comfortable with this site’s process of gathering information from users, and we want you to know exactly how that information is used and what your rights are with regards to all of the information collected.
This Privacy Statement is intended to educate parents and youngsters about the steps they can take to safeguard their privacy when visiting Long Island Junior Soccer League Online or any of the other exciting websites that have links to and from Long Island Junior Soccer League Online. We also hope that the information presented here demonstrates our total commitment to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (“”COPPA””). In doing so, the following discloses our information collection and dissemination practices for this website: www.lijsoccer.com.
If you have any concern that Long Island Junior Soccer League Online is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should e-mail the site administrator, Ken Ilchuk, at keneye@optonline.net, or use the contact information below:
Long Island Junior Soccer League701-9 Koehler AvenueRonkonkoma, NY 11779631-648-9020EMAIL
Information Collection and Use
Long Island Junior Soccer League Online collects information from our users at several different points, and is the sole owner of the data collected on the website. In each case, only information that is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity at hand will be sought. For example, Long Island Junior Soccer League Online will not ask children for their home mailing address in order to receive an e-mailed newsletter. We will never condition a child’s participation in an online activity on the disclosure of information that is beyond what is reasonably necessary for Long Island Junior Soccer League Online to conduct the applicable activity.
Using the Parent’s Information Access Form available on this site, a parent may, at any time, review any identifiable information collected from their child, and may choose to have some or all of the information deleted from Long Island Junior Soccer League Online’s database. Parents may also consent to the internal use of their child’s personal information while declining to permit the site to share this data with third parties.
Register Links
Long Island Junior Soccer League Online may require users to register in order to participate in certain areas of the web site. This includes, but is not limited to the Tryout Forum, and any area that requires submission of content or participation. The content of www.lijsoccer.com is appropriate for all ages. However, we encourage parents to read and become familiar with the privacy policies and information collection practices of this and all sites that their children enter. To register on the site, a user is asked to give various contact information. This should only be done by users over the age of 13. Information collected by Long Island Junior Soccer League Online will not be transferred, disclosed or otherwise shared with third parties. However, LIJSL may send e-mail correspondence on behalf of 3rd party sponsor groups. In addition to e-mailing subscribers, we may send a “”welcoming e-mail”” to first-time visitors, and occasional updates to keep users current on the site-specific services, event calendars, regional competition news, and other points of interest including periodic special offers from Long Island Junior Soccer League Online. Our intent in collecting information from users is to provide the most personalized and rewarding online experience possible. Always keeping privacy in mind, we give parents the option to decline or “”opt-out”” of these types of e-mailed communications at the same point where we request information about the visitor on the page where information is collected. At any time, if you would like to “”unsubscribe”” or would prefer that you or your child’s information be removed from our database, and/or you do not want to receive future communications from Long Island Junior Soccer League Online or our partners, you may send an e-mail request to our site administrator,  EMAIL, or use the contact information below:
Long Island Junior Soccer League701-9 Koehler AvenueRonkonkoma, NY 11779631-648-9020EMAIL
Surveys
From time to time, Long Island Junior Soccer League Online conducts user surveys on a variety of youth soccer-related topics. Our website will advise users that participation in these surveys is completely voluntary, and there is no requirement to disclose any personally identifiable information. All surveys conducted through this site will be used as research for the purposes of assessing and improving user satisfaction, and/or for determining the user’s opinion on a particular issue relating to LIJSL or the sport of soccer generally. Survey information collected may be shared with third parties in an aggregated manner for the purposes of showing sponsors of LIJSL and people in the soccer community what the opinions of our members are on particular subjects. However, the information collected in these surveys will not be used for commercial solicitation purposes without the express consent of users completing the survey. Each survey will give users the choice to “”opt-in”” to receiving messages from advertisers or sponsors by checking a box on the appropriate page.
Contests and Sweepstakes
Long Island Junior Soccer League Online occasionally offers contests and sweepstakes that may be entered directly through the site or through a linked site. As with all other interactive elements of this site, participation in contests and sweepstakes is completely voluntary, and the user can choose not to disclose information. Users who wish to enter a contest or sweepstakes will be asked to provide information necessary to conduct the operation and fulfillment of the contest or sweepstakes. Generally, this includes the participant’s name, age, mailing address, e-mail address (optional) and telephone number. Participants will not be asked to provide any other personal information unless it is reasonably necessary to ensure the participant’s registration, eligibility of the entrant, the notification of winners and the awarding of prizes. Parents may be asked to provide similar information, along with their consent to permit their child(ren) to enter a contest or sweepstakes, and to sign documents related to the awarding of prizes. All information collected by Long Island Junior Soccer League Online in connection with sweepstakes or contests is securely maintained until the conclusion of the contest or sweepstakes, at which time it is deleted from the site’s database. Information needed to notify the winners and to award prizes will be gathered by Long Island Junior Soccer League Online and forwarded to the Long Island Junior Soccer League Office. However, information collected from users in connection with contests and sweepstakes may also be dispensed to a third-party fulfillment house for the limited purpose of awarding prizes to contest and sweepstakes winners, or to applicable regulatory officials for the purposes of complying with applicable laws. Entities that provide fulfillment services will be instructed to maintain the confidentiality of such information and not to use the information for any purpose outside of the function they have been asked to perform.
Information Sharing
Long Island Junior Soccer League Online may accumulate and store aggregated demographic information about its users. This information is not linked or otherwise traceable to any identifiable personal information, and is used solely to advise website partners and advertisers of the site’s general audience characteristics and track responses to online programs and activities.
When called upon to do so, Long Island Junior Soccer League Online will disclose information received as required by law, for example, in response to a court order or other specific requests by law enforcement agencies. We will not sell, share, or rent personally identifiable information to others in any way that violates this Privacy Statement or that otherwise jeopardizes the security and integrity of the information collected. However, we may use the personal information received from the users who have “opted in” to have sponsors, manufacturers and/or distributors contact them (through the LIJSL) about such things as sales and special offers. We will seek verifiable parental consent prior to sharing information in any manner that differs materially from the practices described herein.
In addition, if all or substantially all of the assets relating to www.lijsoccer.com are transferred or sold to another entity, personal information we received from users may be transferred to the acquiring entity.
Parental Access/Control of Information
In compliance with COPPA, any parent of a child who provides information to Long Island Junior Soccer League Online has the right to review the child’s personal information, order its deletion, and refuse to allow further collection or use of the child’s information.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Long Island Junior Soccer League Online does not use cookies to operate our site.
Some of our business partners use cookies on their sites (for example, sponsors). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.
Log Files
Long Island Junior Soccer League Online may use Internet Protocol addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Security/Links
This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. We do not ask our users for more information than is necessary to conduct the various activities being conducted on our website, and all of our information is protected both online and off-line through the use of industry-standard practices. Long Island Junior Soccer League Online encourages visitors to familiarize themselves, not only with this Privacy Statement, but also to review and understand the privacy policies and information collection practices of other websites that link to and from this site. While Long Island Junior Soccer League Online screens our links for overall content, information and entertainment value, we are not responsible for the practices of other sites as they apply to privacy, security, integrity and compliance with COPPA. This Privacy Statement applies solely to information collected by this website.
If you have any questions or would like more information about the security at our website, you can send an e-mail to our site administrator: EMAIL, or use the contact information below:
Long Island Junior Soccer League701-9 Koehler AvenueRonkonkoma, NY 11779631-648-9020EMAIL
User Submissions
This site provides users with an opportunity to submit their own articles and comments on soccer for possible online publication. Long Island Junior Soccer League Online reserves the right to edit user submissions for appropriate language, content, space, and other editorial considerations. Full names and contact information from the submissions are not used on the site unless permission is granted by the submitter.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post a prominent link to those changes on the home page of Long Island Junior Soccer League Online for ninety (90) days so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in a different manner. In using information, Long Island Junior Soccer League Online will always adhere to the most recent version of this Privacy Statement.
Contacting the Website
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, or the practices of this site, or wish to modify or delete information previously submitted, please e-mail our site administrator, Ken Ilchuk, at: kenlijsl@ix.netcom.com, or use the contact information below:
Long Island Junior Soccer League701-9 Koehler AvenueRonkonkoma, NY 11779631-648-9020EMAIL
Legal Statement
All content and images on youthsoccer.org are owned by Long Island Junior Soccer League unless credited to a partner. Any re-use of the content and images is forbidden without consent from the site administrator, Ken Ilchuk, available at EMAIL.
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish. Cookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
